In an internal memo from September, CEO Sam Altman said that OpenAI's audacious long-term
goal is, audacious is the word, is to build 250 gigawatts of capacity by 2033.
If Altman achieves this goal, OpenAI will need almost exactly as much electricity as
India's 1.5 billion people and is likely to emit nearly twice as much carbon dioxide as
ExxonMobil, the world's largest non-state carbon emitter via Alan Kirk, PCA, Premaculture,
Climate Action.
Audacious is the operative word here because it's the audacity of all of these capitalists,
particularly white men, to just feel like, F it.
My ambition is just far more valuable than like the planet.
And all of you all who keep using AI super cash, like, cut it out.
Stop.
Like, if you can't write, just don't be a writer.
These men are a cancer that has unlimited growth unless we become the method that stops them.
Doesn't it bother you?
It's a filth fest in the dark of early morn.